microcapmagazine.com 2016-10-30

# Privacy Policy - MicroCapMagazine

Our Privacy Policy:

> MicroCap Group, LLC (“MicroCap Group, LLC”) administers the MicroCapMagazine.com and may also handle other websites. Our policy is to respect your privacy regarding any kind of information we collect while you are operating our websites.

For Website Visitors:

> Alike most of the websites, MicroCap Group, LLC collects non-personally identifiable information, which web browsers and servers usually make available, such as browser types, language preferences, referring sites, and the date and time of each visitor’s request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifiable information is for better understanding how our visitors use websites. Every once in a while MicroCap Group, LLC may release non-personally identifiable information in the aggregates, e.g., by publishing a usage report on trends in the website.
> 
> MicroCap Group, LLC also collects personally identifiable information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on MicroCapMagazine.com blogs/sites. MicroCap Group, LLC only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the similar circumstances of how it uses and discloses personally identifiable information as described in below, except that the commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

Gathering of Personally Identifiable Information

> Certain visitors to our websites, who choose to interact with MicroCap Group, LLC in a way that MicroCap Group, LLC, had to gather personally identifiable information. The type and the extent of information that MicroCap Group, LLC gathers depend on the nature of interaction visitor did. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at MicroCapMagazine.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with MicroCap Group, LLC are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, MicroCap Group, LLC collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with MicroCap Group, LLC. MicroCap Group, LLC does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to provide any personally identifiable information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics

> MicroCap Group, LLC may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. MicroCap Group, LLC may display collected information publicly or privately. However, MicroCap Group, LLC does not disclose personally identifiable information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally Identifiable Information

> MicroCap Group, LLC discloses potentially personally identifiable and personally identifiable information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at our websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. MicroCap Group, LLC will not rent or sell personally identifiable and personally identifiable information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, MicroCap Group, LLC discloses potentially personally identifiable and personally identifiable information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental requests, or when MicroCap Group, LLC believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of MicroCap Group, LLC, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a MicroCap Group, LLC website and have supplied your email address, MicroCap Group, LLC may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with MicroCap Group, LLC and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. MicroCap Group, LLC takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifiable and personally identifiable information.

Cookies

> A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. MicroCap Group, LLC uses cookies to help MicroCap Group, LLC identifies and track visitors, their usage of MicroCap Group, LLC website, and their website access preferences. MicroCap Group, LLC visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our websites, with the drawback that certain features of our websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Business Transfers

> If MicroCap Group, LLC, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that MicroCap Group, LLC goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that are transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any acquirer of MicroCap Group, LLC may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Ads

> Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MicroCap Group, LLC and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Privacy Policy Changes

> Although most changes are likely to be minor, MicroCap Group, LLC may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. MicroCap Group, LLC encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a MicroCapMagazine.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
